第一个问题：XML 元素的名字在这里：TextView
The answer to the first question is that the XML element name is here, TextView.
在左尖括号的后面
It follows the open angle bracket.
随后 所有的属性都在XML元素的下方
Then, all the attributes are below the XML element name, and
我在此已经用下划线标注出了这些属性的名称
I've underlined the attribute names here.
它们在等号的左边
They're on the left hand side of the equal sign.
它们包括 android:text android:textColor 等等
They include android:text, android:textColor, and so on.
如果你填写的是属性值 如"Happy Birthday"或者"color/white"
If you put the attribute values, like Happy Birthday or the color/white or
或是"black" 这是错的 因为他们是属性值
black, that's incorrect, because those are the attribute values, and
而问的问题是属性名称
it's asking for the names.
最后一个问题是 标签在哪一行结束？
The last question is, on what line number is a tag closed?
我们可以看到斜杠
Then we see the forward slash and
和右尖括号在最后一行 那是第六行
the closing angle bracket on the last line, which is line 6.
这就是说 这是一个自关闭标签
This means that it's a self-closing tag,
因为我们在这里开始标签 并在这里立刻关闭了它
because we open the text view tag here and then we close it right away.